# **Front End Developer**

# JAKE KNOWLES

✓ jakeyknowles@hotmail.co.uk

**Q** 07947108062

complex iknowles 94

## **EXPERIENCE**

#### **IPUSHPULL**

#### Front-End Developer | since April 2019

Migrated the main web app from AngularJS to Vue and build a reusable component architecture to use throughout other intergrations such as Symphony and Microsoft Teams. Implement a continuous integration while running tests using Cypress and Bitbucket Pipelines.

## Amigo Partnership

### Front-End Developer | August 2015 - April 2019

I was working in a small development team of 6 to create and develop a bespoke CMS using AngularJS and our own API using GraphQL/Rails. I am responsible for leading a team to deliver a bespoke CMS and web app (including a native app, using Cordova), on a range of clients, such as, Rolls-Royce, O2 and Xcina. I am assisting with the growth of the company, to help improve the workflow and production throughout the development team in order to work more efficiently.

#### Mccormack & Morrison

#### Junior Front-End and Email Developer | October 2013 - July 2015

Building and maintaining websites and landing pages for companies using wordpress. Creating responsive emails and newsletters that work over multiple platforms.

#### **Contentive**

#### Web Developer Apprentice | September 2012 - October 2013

Building, testing and maintaining business standard websites for clients including Landing pages and HTML Email Templates.

# **EDUCATION**

# Level 3 Diploma

IT Professional (Web Development) | August 2012 - August 2013

#### A Level

ICT- BTEC National, History, Media Studies | September 2010 - May 2012

#### CKILL C

# About me

Enthusiastic and creative Front-end web developer with over 5 years of experience. I am knowledgeable in a range of Front-end languages and tools to build and maintain a wide range of web applications. I am a dependable team player and keen learner who thrives when faced with learning new tools which enhance my professional skillset.